streamingfaith.com 2013-06-30

# Online Privacy Policy | Streaming Faith

Privacy is of great concern to most users of the Internet, and is a critical part of an enjoyable and satisfactory user experience. We at Streaming Faith are acutely aware of and sensitive to the privacy concerns of our subscribers and other visitors to our Web site (the "Web Site"). Whether you are a customer of our various products and services or merely a visitor to our site, we assure you that we do not collect personal information from you unless you provide it to us and do not provide or sell personal information to entities that are outside of the Streaming Faith family.

##  The Information We Collect

On certain pages of the Web Site, you can order products, enter contests, vote in polls or otherwise express an opinion, subscribe to one of our services such as our online newsletters, or participate in one of our online forums or communities. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected at these pages include: name, address, e-mail address, telephone number, and information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services.

On other pages of the Web Site, you can submit information about other people. For example, you might submit a person's name and e-mail address to send an article or devotional and, if you order a gift online and want it sent directly to the recipient, you might submit the recipient's name and address. The types of personally identifiable information that may be collected about other people at these pages include: recipient's name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number.

On certain parts of our Web Site, only persons who provide us with the requested personally identifiable information will be able to view or listen to certain content, order products, programs, and services or otherwise participate in the Web Site's activities and offerings.

We also may collect certain non-personally identifiable information when you visit many of our web pages such as the type of browser you are using (e.g., Firefox, Safari, Internet Explorer), the type of operating system you are using, (e.g., Windows XP or Mac OS X) and the domain name of your Internet service provider (e.g., AT&T, Earthlink).

##  How We Use the Information

We may use the information you provide about yourself to fulfill your requests for our products, programs, and services, to respond to your inquiries about our offerings, to provide you access to special functionality and features on our Web Site and to offer you other products, programs or services that we believe may be of interest to you.

We sometimes use this information to communicate with you, such as to fulfill a request by you for an online newsletter or to contact you about your membership with us.

We use the information that you provide about others to enable us to send them your gifts, articles or devotionals. From time to time, we also may use this information to offer our products, programs, or services to them or send them information from members of the Streaming Faith broadcast family.

The information we collect in connection with our online forums and communities is used to provide an interactive experience. We use this information to facilitate participation in these online forums and communities and, from time to time, to offer you products, programs, or services.

We sometimes use the non-personally identifiable information that we collect to improve the design and content of our site and to enable us to personalize your Internet experience. We also may use this information in the aggregate to analyze site usage, as well as to offer you products, programs, or services.

We may disclose personally identifiable information in response to legal process, for example, in response to a court order or a subpoena. We also may disclose such information in response to a law enforcement agency's request, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding illegal activities, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, violations of our terms of use, or as otherwise required by law. In addition, we may transfer information about you if we are acquired by or merged with another company.

Agents and contractors of Streaming Faith who have access to personally identifiable information are required to protect this information in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Notice by, for example, not using the information for any purpose other than to carry out the services they are performing for Streaming Faith.

Although we take appropriate measures to safeguard against unauthorized disclosures of information, we cannot assure you that personally identifiable information that we collect will never be disclosed in a manner that is inconsistent with this Privacy Notice.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to members of the Streaming Faith broadcast family whose practices are not covered by this privacy notice (e.g., ministries and other providers of content available on the Web Site) that want to provide you with information or market products or services to you.

We may on occasion combine information we receive online with outside records to enhance our ability to market to you those products or services that may be of interest to you. However, we will provide you with a way to opt out of these kinds of offers.

Finally, the Web Site by this Privacy Notice will not use or transfer personally identifiable information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

##  Cookies & Web Beacons

To enhance your experience with our Web Site, many of our web pages use "cookies." Cookies are text files we place in your computer's browser to store your preferences. Cookies, by themselves, do not tell us your e-mail address or other personally identifiable information unless you choose to provide this information to us by, for example, registering at one of our sites. However, once you choose to furnish our Web Sitewith personally identifiable information, this information may be linked to the data stored in the cookie.

We use cookies to understand site usage and to improve the content and offerings on our sites. For example, we may use cookies to personalize your experience at our web pages (e.g., to recognize you by name when you return to our site), save your password in password-protected areas, and enable you to use shopping carts on our sites. We also may use cookies to offer you products, programs, or services.

"Web beacons" or clear .gifs are small pieces of code placed on a web page to monitor the behavior and collect data about the visitors viewing a web page. For example, web beacons can be used to count the users who visit a web page or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a visitor viewing that page. We may use web beacons on this site from time to time for this and other purposes.

##  Collection of Information by Third-Party Sites, Ad Servers, and Sponsors

Some of the pages on the Web Site contain links to other sites whose information practices may be different than ours. Visitors to our Web Site should consult the other sites' privacy notices as we have no control over information that is submitted to, or collected by, these third parties.

Streaming Faith may sometimes offer content (e.g., contests, sweepstakes, or promotions) that is sponsored by or co-branded with identified third parties. By virtue of these relationships, the third parties may obtain personally identifiable information that visitors voluntarily submit to participate in the site activity. Streaming Faith has no control over these third parties' use of this information. Streaming Faith will notify you at the time of requesting personally identifiable information if these third parties will obtain such information.

Streaming Faith may use a reputable third party to present or serve the advertisements that you may see at its Web pages. These third party ad servers may use cookies, web beacons, clear .gifs or similar technologies to help present such advertisements, and to help measure and research the advertisements' effectiveness. The use of these technologies by these third party ad servers is subject to their own privacy policies and is not covered by our privacy policy.

##  Our Commitment to Security

We have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the information we collect online.

##  How You can Access or Correct Information

You can access or modify the personally identifiable information that this Web Site has collected about you by logging into the Web Site and viewing or editing your profile. To protect your privacy and security, we will take reasonable steps to help verify your identity before granting access or making corrections.

##  Special Note for Parents

The site you are visiting is a general audience site. It is not intended for children and we do not collect personally identifiable information from children.

##  How to Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about the Streaming Faith online policy for this site or its implementation you may contact us at [privacy@streamingfaith.com](mailto:privacy@streamingfaith.com).

##  Updates & Effective Date

From time to time, we may update this privacy notice. We will notify you about material changes in the way we treat personally identifiable information by placing a notice on our site. We encourage you to periodically check back and review this policy so that you always will know what information we collect, how we use it, and to whom we disclose it.

The Privacy Notice posted on this site was updated on or about June 1, 2008.
